http://www.safetyfile.com/pages/privacy-policy-conditions-of-use

All ProductsFireKing Fireproof Data Safes FireProof Data Safes-3 hourFireProof Data Safes-2 hourFireProof Data Safes-1 hourFireKing Personal Media SafesFireproof File Cabinets Fireproof Files-Vertical FireKing 2 Hour Vertical FilesFireKing 31" depth VerticalFireKing 25" depth VerticalFireKing 22" depth Turtle filePatriot by FireKingFireproof Files-LateralFireKing Document CabinetSafe in a Fireproof FileFireproof Card FilesFireKing safes Media Safes FireProof Data Safes-3 HourFireProof Data Safes-2 HourFireProof Data Safes-1 hourMedia Safes-PersonalFireProof safe-1 Hour BurglaryFireproof safe-2 hour BurglaryHigh Security SafesFire and water resistant safesHigh Security SafesDeposit SafesSafe in a Fireproof FileSafe in a Fireproof FileFireking Document CabinetFireproof Waterproof File SafesSpecialty SafesAbout SafetyFileContact Us
1-800-700-8025
Privacy Policy/Conditions of Use
Information Collection and Use
SafetyFile LLC. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others not directly involved in processing, shipping, billing, or customer service issues pertaining to orders or inquires.
SafetyFile maintains a strict policy AGAINST SPAM. We will only send email pertaining to a purchase, product inquiry or update.
E-CommerceWe request information from the user in order to process, bill and ship orders. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user for confirmation and communications regarding a customers order or inquiry.
CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user"s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.
Log FilesWe use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
SharingWe may use an outside shipping company to ship orders {drop ship }, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may also partner with another party to provide specific services. We will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services [freight companies, moving companies, locksmiths for warranty or field repair services etc}.
These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
LinksThis web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that SafetyFile LLC. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
SurveysFrom time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and the products sold.
SecurityThis website takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our shopping cart/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers information is protected.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to info@safetyfile.com.
Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected ,this page will be promptly updated. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
